Guide to the Rand School of Social Science Records TAM.007
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series VI: Publications, 1906-1955; 113546
  - Subseries VID: Index to Labor Articles, 1926- 1953, 113833
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 16, no. 9-10, Sep 1942-Oct 1942; 113889 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 16, no. 11-12, Nov 1942-Dec 1942; 113888 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 17, no. 1-2, Jan 1943-Feb 1943; 113887 (Box 55, Folder 4)
      Film R-7124, Reel 53: Frame XIII:F:4:1943
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 17, no. 3-4, Mar 1943-Apr 1943; 113886 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 17, no. 5-6, May 1943-Jun 1943; 113885 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 17, no. 7-8, Jul 1943-Aug 1943; 113884 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 17, no. 9-10, Sep 1943-Oct 1943; 113883 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 17, no. 11-12, Nov 1943-Dec 1943; 113882 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 18, no. 1-2, Jan 1944-Feb 1944; 113881 (Box 55, Folder 5)
      Film R-7124, Reel 53: Frame XIII:F:4:1944
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 18, no. 3-4, Mar 1944-Apr 1944; 113880 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 18, no. 5-6, May 1944-Jun 1944; 113879 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 18, no. 7-8, Jul 1944-Aug 1944; 113878 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 18, no. 9-10, Sep 1944-Oct 1944; 113877 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 18, no. 11-12, Nov 1944-Dec 1944; 113876 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 19, no. 1-2, Jan 1945-Feb 1945; 113875 (Box 55, Folder 6)
      Film R-7124, Reel 53: Frame XIII:F:4:1945
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 19, no. 3-4, Mar 1945-Apr 1945; 113874 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 19, no. 5-6, May 1945-Jun 1945; 113873 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 19, no. 7-8, Jul 1945-Aug 1945; 113872 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 19, no. 9-10, Sep 1945-Oct 1945; 113871 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 19, no. 11-12, Nov 1945-Dec 1945; 113870 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 20, no. 1-2, Feb 1946; 113869 (Box 55, Folder 7)
      Film R-7124, Reel 53: Frame XIII:F:4:1946
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 20, no. 3-4, Mar 1946-Apr 1946; 113868 (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 20, no. 5-6, Dec 1946; 113867 (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 21, no. 1, Feb 1947; 113866 (Box 55, Folder 8)
      Film R-7124, Reel 53: Frame XIII:F:4:1947
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 21, no. 2, Mar 1947-Apr 1947; 113865 (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 21, no. 3, Dec 1947; 113864 (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 22, no. 13-14 [sic], Jan 1948-Feb 1948; 113863 (Box 55, Folder 9)
      Film R-7124, Reel 53: Frame XIII:F:4:1948
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 22, no.3-4, Mar 1948-Apr 1948; 113862 (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 22, no.5-6, May 1948-Jun 1948; 113861 (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 22, no.7-8, Jul 1948-Aug 1948; 113860 (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 22, no.9-10, Sep 1948-Oct 1948; 113859 (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 23, no.1-2, Jan 1949-Feb 1949; 113858 (Box 55, Folder 10)
      Film R-7124, Reel 53: Frame XIII:F:4:1949
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 23, no.3-4, Mar 1949-Apr 1949; 113857 (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 23, no.5-6, May 1949-Jun 1949; 113856 (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 23, no.7-8, Jul 1949-Aug 1949; 113855 (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 23, no.9-10, Sep 1949-Oct 1949; 113854 (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 23, no.11-12, Nov 1949-Dec 1949; 113853 (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 24, no. 1-2, Jan 1950-Feb 1950; 113852 (Box 55, Folder 11)
      Film R-7124, Reel 53: Frame XIII:F:4:1950
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 24, no. 3-4, Mar 1950-Apr 1950; 113851 (Box 55, Folder 11)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 24, no. 5-6, May 1950-Jun 1950; 113850 (Box 55, Folder 11)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 24, no. 7-8, Jul 1950-Aug 1950; 113849 (Box 55, Folder 11)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 24, no. 9-10, Sep 1950-Oct 1950; 113848 (Box 55, Folder 11)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 24, no. 11-12, Nov 1950-Dec 1950; 113847 (Box 55, Folder 11)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 25, no. 1-2, Jan 1951-Feb 1951; 113846 (Box 55, Folder 12)
      Film R-7124, Reel 53: Frame XIII:F:4:1951
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 25, no. 3-4, Mar 1951-Apr 1951; 113845 (Box 55, Folder 12)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 25, no. 5-6, May 1951-Jun 1951; 113844 (Box 55, Folder 12)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 25, no. 7-8, Jul 1951-Aug 1951; 113843 (Box 55, Folder 12)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 25, no. 9-10, Sep 1951-Oct 1951; 113842 (Box 55, Folder 12)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 25, no. 11-11/v. 26, no. 1-2 (combined issue), Nov 1951-Dec 1951; 113841 (Box 55, Folder 12)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 26, no. 1-2, Jan 1952-Feb 1952; 113840 (Box 56, Folder 1)
      Film R-7124, Reel 53: Frame XIII:F:4:1952
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 26, no. 3-4, Mar 1952-Apr 1952; 113839 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 26, no. 5-6, May 1952-Jun 1952; 113838 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 26, no. 9-10/11-12 (combined issue), Sep 1952-Dec 1952; 113837 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 27, no. 1-2, Jan 1953-Feb 1953; 113836 (Box 56, Folder 2)
      Film R-7124, Reel 53: Frame XIII:F:4:1953
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 27, no. 3-4/5-6 (combined issue), Mar 1953-Jun 1953; 113835 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 27, no. 7-8/9-10 (combined issue), Jul 1953-Oct 1953; 113834 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Subseries VIE: Serials, 1918-1955, 113723
    The serials part of the publications series contains nine short lived internal publications. The most prominent serial publications in this part include the Institute of Social Studies Bulletin(XIII:F:5:1), The Labor student(XIII:8:5:3), The Rand School News(XIII:F:5:7), Russian Affairs(before it was incorporated into the New Leader;XIII:F:5:8), and The Student Worker(XIII:F:5:9). The serials are arranged in alphabetical order according to the title of the publication. Separate issues within a particular serial are arranged in chronological order. A full bibliographical citation for each serial can be found in the complete reel list for this collection.
    - Bulletin: Institute of Social Studies, v. 1, no. 1, Feb 1951; 113832 (Box 56, Folder 3)
      Film R-7124, Reel 53: Frame XIII:F:5:1
    - Bulletin: Institute of Social Studies, v. 1, no. 2, May 1951; 113831 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Bulletin: Institute of Social Studies, v. 1, no. 3, Oct 1951; 113830 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Bulletin: Institute of Social Studies, v. 1, no. 4, Jan 1952; 113829 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Bulletin: Institute of Social Studies, v. 1, no. 5, Spring 1952; 113828 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Bulletin: Institute of Social Studies, v. 1, no. 6, Summer 1952; 113827 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Bulletin: Institute of Social Studies, v. 1, no. 7, Fall 1952; 113826 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Bulletin: Institute of Social Studies, v. 1, no. 8, Winter 1952; 113825 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Bulletin: Institute of Social Studies, v. 2, no. 1, Spring 1953; 113824 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Bulletin: Institute of Social Studies, v. 2, no. 2, Summer 1953; 113823 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Bulletin: Institute of Social Studies, v. 2, no. 3, Fall 1953; 113822 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Bulletin: Institute of Social Studies, v. 2, no. 4, Winter 1953; 113821 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Bulletin: Institute of Social Studies, v. 2, no. 5, Spring 1954; 113820 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Bulletin: Institute of Social Studies, v. 2, no. 6, Summer 1954; 113819 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Bulletin: Institute of Social Studies, v. 2, no. 7, Fall 1954; 113818 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Bulletin: Institute of Social Studies, v. 2, no. 8, Winter 1954; 113817 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Bulletin: Institute of Social Studies, v. 3, no. 1, Spring 1955; 113816 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Bulletin: Institute of Social Studies, v. 3, no. 2, Summer 1955; 113815 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Bulletin: Institute of Social Studies, v. 3, no. 3, Fall 1955; 113814 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Bulletin: Womens Committee of the Rand School of Social Science, v. 1, no. 2, Jan 1934; 113813 (Box 56, Folder 4)
      Film R-7124, Reel 53: Frame XIII:F:5:2
    - Bulletin: Womens Committee of the Rand School of Social Science, v. 1, no. 3, Feb 1934; 113812 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Bulletin: Womens Committee of the Rand School of Social Science, v. 1, no. 4, Mar 1934; 113811 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - The Labor Student, v. 1, no. 1, Jan 1925; 113810 (Box 56, Folder 5)
      Film R-7124, Reel 53: Frame XIII:F:5:3
    - The Labor Student, v. 1, no. 2, Feb 1925; 113809 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - The Labor Student, v. 1, no. 3-4, Mar 1925-Apr 1925; 113808 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - The Labor Student, v. 1, no. 4, Aug 1925; 113807 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - The Labor Student, v. 1, no. 5, Jun 1926-Jul 1926; 113806 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - The Labor Student, v. 1, no. 6, Dec 1926; 113805 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - The Labor Student, v. 1, no. 7, Jun 1927; 113804 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - The Rand Rambler, v. 1, no. 1, Nov 1929; 113803 (Box 56, Folder 6)
      Film R-7124, Reel 53: Frame XIII:F:5:4
    - Rand School Advance, v. 1, no. [1], Oct 1937; 113802 (Box 56, Folder 7)
      Film R-7124, Reel 53: Frame XIII:F:5:5
    - Rand School Advance, v. 1, no. 2, Nov 1937; 113801 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Rand School Advance, v. 1, no. 3, Dec 1937; 113800 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Rand School Advance, v. 1, no. 4 (lacks v. 1, no. 4), Jan 1938; 113799 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Rand School Advance, v. 1, no. 5, Feb 1938; 113798 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Rand School Advance, v. 1, no. 6, Mar 1938; 113797 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Rand School Advance, v. 1, no. 6 [sic], Apr 1938; 113796 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Rand School Fellowship Bulletin, v. 1, no. 1, Mar 14, 1925; 113795 (Box 56, Folder 8)
      Film R-7124, Reel 53: Frame XIII:F:5:6
    - Rand School News, v. 1, no. 1, ca. Feb 19, 1918; 113794 (Box 56, Folder 9)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:5:7
    - Rand School News, v. 1, no. 2, Mar 1918; 113793 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Rand School News, v. 1, no. 3, May 1918; 113792 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Rand School News, v. 1, no. 4, Jun 1918; 113791 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Rand School News, v. 1, no. 5, Nov 1918; 113790 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Rand School News, v. 1, no. 6, Dec 1918; 113789 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Rand School News, v. 2, no. 2, Feb 1919; 113788 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Rand School News, v. 2, no. 3, Apr 1919; 113787 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Rand School News, v. 2, no. 4, Jun 1919; 113786 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Rand School News, v. 3, no. 1, Sep 1919; 113785 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Rand School News, v. 3, no. 2, Jan 1920; 113784 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Rand School News and Book Review, v. 1, no. 1, Sep 1920; 113783 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Rand School News and Book Review, v. 1, no. 2, Oct 1920; 113782 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Rand School News and Book Review, v. 1, no. 3, Nov 1920; 113781 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Rand School News and Book Review, v. 1, no. 4, Dec 1920; 113780 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Rand School News and Book Review, v. 1, no. 5, Jan 1921; 113779 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Rand School News and Book Review, v. 1, no. 6, Feb 1921; 113778 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Rand School News and Book Review, v. 1, no. 7, Mar 1921; 113777 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Rand School News and Book Review, v. 2, no. 1, Sep 1921; 113776 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Rand School News and Book Review, v. 2, no. 2, Oct 1921-Nov 1921; 113775 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Rand School News and Book Review, v. 2, no. 3, Dec 1921; 113774 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Rand School News and Book Review, v. 2, no. 4, Jan 1922-Feb 1922; 113773 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Rand School News and Book Review, v. 2, no. 5, Mar 1922; 113772 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Rand School News and Book Review, v. 2, no. 6, Oct 1922; 113771 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Rand School News and Book Review, v. 2, no. 7, Nov 1922; 113770 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Rand School News and Book Review, v. 2, no. 8, Dec 1922; 113769 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Rand School News and Book Review, v. 2, no. 8A, Dec 1922; 113768 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Rand School News and Book Review, v. 3, no. 1, Jun 1923; 113767 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Rand School News and Book Review, v. 3, no. 2, Sep 1923; 113766 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Rand School News and Book Review, v. 3, no. 3, Oct 1923; 113765 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Rand School News and Book Review, v. 3, no. 4, Dec 1923; 113764 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Rand School News and Book Review, v. 4, no. 1, Aug 1924; 113763 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Rand School News and Book Review, v. 4, no. 2, Sep 1924; 113762 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Rand School News and Book Review, v. 4, no. 3, Oct 1924-Nov 1924; 113761 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Rand School News and Book Review, v. (?), no. 1, Nov 1934; 113760 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Rand School News and Book Review, v. 5, no. 1, Sep 1939; 113759 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Rand School News and Book Review, v. 5, no. 1 [sic], Oct 1939; 113758 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Rand School News and Book Review, v. 5, no. 2, Nov 1939; 113757 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Rand School News and Book Review, v. 5, no. 3, Dec 1939; 113756 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Russian Affairs, v. 1 no. 1, Oct 1944; 113755 (Box 56, Folder 10)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:5:8
    - Russian Affairs, v. 1 no. 2, Nov 1944; 113754 (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - Russian Affairs, v. 1 no. 3, Dec 1944; 113753 (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - Russian Affairs, v. 1 no. 4, Jan 1945; 113752 (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - Russian Affairs, v. 1 no. 5, Mar 1945; 113751 (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - Russian Affairs, v. 1 no. 6, Apr 1945; 113750 (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - Russian Affairs, v. 1 no. 7, May 1945; 113749 (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - Russian Affairs, v. 1 no. 8, Jul 1945; 113748 (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - Russian Affairs, v. 1 no. 9, Oct 1945; 113747 (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - The Student Worker, v. 1, no. 1, Jan 6, 1932; 113746 (Box 56, Folder 11)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:5:9
    - The Student Worker, v. 1, no. 2, Jan 18, 1932; 113745 (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - The Student Worker, v. 1, no. 3, Jan 27, 1932; 113744 (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - The Student Worker, v. 1, no. 4, Feb 1, 1932; 113743 (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - The Student Worker, v. 1, no. 5, Feb 8, 1932; 113742 (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - The Student Worker, v. 1, no. 6, Feb 15, 1932; 113741 (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - The Student Worker, v. 1, no. 7, Feb 24, 1932; 113740 (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - The Student Worker, v. 1, no. 8, Mar 2, 1932; 113739 (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - The Student Worker, v. 1, no. 9, Mar 9, 1932; 113738 (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - The Student Worker, v. 1, no. 10, Mar 16, 1932; 113737 (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - The Student Worker, v. 1, no. 11, Mar 23, 1932; 113736 (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - The Student Worker, v. 1, no. 12, Mar 30, 1932; 113735 (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - The Student Worker, v. 1, no. 13, Apr 6, 1932; 113734 (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - The Student Worker, v. 1, no. 14, Apr 13, 1932; 113733 (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - The Student Worker, v. 2, no. 1, Sep 23, 1932; 113732 (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - The Student Worker, v. 3, no. 1, Sep 26, 1932; 113731 (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - The Student Worker, v. 2, no. 5, Oct 10, 1932; 113730 (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - The Student Worker, v. 2, no. 6, Oct 17, 1932; 113729 (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - The Student Worker, v. 1, no. 2, Feb 1, 1933; 113728 (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - The Student Worker, v. 1, no. 3, Feb 8, 1933; 113727 (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - The Student Worker, v. 1, no. 4, Feb 21, 1933; 113726 (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - The Student Worker, v. 1, no. 5, Feb 28, 1933; 113725 (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - The Student Worker, v. 1, no. 5 [sic], Mar 14, 1933; 113724 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Subseries VIF: Course Bulletins and Announcements, 1906-1955, 113567
    The course bulletins and announcements part of the publications series consists of 155 items. These bulletins pertain to the general course curriculum of the Rand School from 1906 to 1955, and to such special education programs as the Trade Union Institute, the Physical Education Department, summer school, the Workers' Training Course, correspondence courses, Rand High School, Alertness Courses, Political Training Courses, the Newark School of Social Science, the Rand School of Northern New Jersey, and the Trade Union Leadership Training Program. The items in this part are arranged in chronological order. A full bibliographical citation for each item in this part is located in the complete reel list for this collection.
    - Rand School Prospectus, Jul 15, 1906; 113722 (Box 56, Folder 12)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:1
    - First Year Bulletin for First Term, Oct 1, 1906-Dec 23, 1906; 113721 (Box 56, Folder 12)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:2
    - Second Year Bulletin for First Term, Sep 30, 1907-Dec 22, 1907; 113720 (Box 56, Folder 12)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:3
    - Third Year Bulletin for First Term, Sep 28, 1908-Dec 20, 1908; 113719 (Box 56, Folder 12)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:4
    - Third Year Bulletin for Second Term, Jan 10, 1909-Apr 30, 1909; 113718 (Box 56, Folder 12)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:5
    - Fourth Year Bulletin for Second Term, Jan 7, 1910-Apr 28, 1910; 113717 (Box 56, Folder 12)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:6
    - Fifth Year Bulletin for Second Term, Jan 3, 1911-Apr 2, 1911; 113716 (Box 56, Folder 12)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:7
    - Sixth Year Bulletin for First Term, Oct 11, 1911-Jan 19, 1912; 113715 (Box 56, Folder 12)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:8
    - Announcement of Courses, 1911-1912; 113714 (Box 56, Folder 12)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:9
    - Sixth Year Supplementary Bulletin, Dec 5, 1911-Jun 7, 1912; 113713 (Box 56, Folder 12)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:10
    - Announcement of Courses, 1912-1913; 113712 (Box 56, Folder 12)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:11
    - Seventh Year Courses, 1912-1913; 113711 (Box 56, Folder 12)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:12
    - Full-Time Courses, 1913-1914; 113710 (Box 56, Folder 12)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:13
    - Courses of Study, 1913-1914; 113709 (Box 56, Folder 12)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:14
    - Bulletin, 1915-1916; 113708 (Box 56, Folder 12)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:15
    - Bulletin, 1916-1917; 113707 (Box 56, Folder 12)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:16
    - Bulletin, 1918-1919; 113704 (Box 56, Folder 12)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:19
    - Bulletin, 1917-1918; 113706 (Box 56, Folder 12)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:17
    - Summer Season of The Rand School, 1918; 113705 (Box 56, Folder 12)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:18
    - Announcement of the Correspondence Department, 1919; 113703 (Box 56, Folder 12)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:20
    - Summer Season of The Rand School, Jul 7, 1919-Aug 16, 1919; 113702 (Box 56, Folder 12)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:21
    - Summer Season of The Rand School, Jul 7, 1919-Aug 16, 1919; 113701 (Box 56, Folder 12)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:22
    - Workers Training Course, undated; 113700 (Box 56, Folder 12)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:23
    - Bulletin, 1919-1920; 113699 (Box 56, Folder 12)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:24
    - Third Summer Session, 1920; 113698 (Box 56, Folder 13)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:25
    - Bulletin, 1920-1921; 113697 (Box 56, Folder 13)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:26
    - Announcement of the Correspondence Department, 1920; 113696 (Box 56, Folder 13)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:27
    - Physical Education Department, 1921-1922; 113695 (Box 56, Folder 13)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:28
    - Bulletin, 1922-1923; 113694 (Box 56, Folder 13)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:29
    - Full-Time Training Course, 1923; 113693 (Box 56, Folder 13)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:30
    - Summer Session, 1923; 113692 (Box 56, Folder 13)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:31
    - Physical Education Department, 1923-1924; 113691 (Box 56, Folder 13)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:32
    - Physical Education Department, 1924-1925; 113690 (Box 56, Folder 13)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:33
    - Courses Now Beginning, 1925-1926; 113689 (Box 56, Folder 13)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:34
    - Physical Education Department Announcement, 1925-1926; 113688 (Box 56, Folder 13)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:35
    - Preliminary Announcement for Courses for Trade Unionists, May 1926; 113687 (Box 56, Folder 13)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:36
    - Schedule of Courses, 1927-1928; 113686 (Box 56, Folder 13)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:37
    - New Courses, 1927; 113685 (Box 56, Folder 13)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:38
    - New Courses, 1927; 113684 (Box 56, Folder 13)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:39
    - New Courses, 1927; 113683 (Box 56, Folder 13)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:40
    - Schedule for Second Term, 1927-1928; 113682 (Box 56, Folder 13)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:41
    - Preliminary Announcement, 1928-1929; 113681 (Box 56, Folder 13)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:42
    - Announcement, 1928-1929; 113680 (Box 56, Folder 13)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:43
    - Mid-Winter Bulletin, Jan 1929; 113679 (Box 56, Folder 13)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:44
    - Twenty-Fourth Season, 1929-1930; 113678 (Box 56, Folder 13)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:45
    - Winter-Spring Twenty-Fourth Season, 1930; 113677 (Box 57, Folder 1)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:46
    - Evening Courses and Lectures: Twenty-Fifth Season, 1931; 113676 (Box 57, Folder 1)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:47
    - Evening Courses and Lectures: Twenty-Fifth Season, 1931; 113675 (Box 57, Folder 1)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:48
    - Winter Courses, 1931; 113674 (Box 57, Folder 1)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:49
    - Preliminary Announcement, 1931-1932; 113673 (Box 57, Folder 1)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:50
    - Evening Courses and Lectures, 1931-1932; 113672 (Box 57, Folder 1)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:51
    - Winter Courses and Lectures, 1932; 113671 (Box 57, Folder 1)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:52
    - 1932-1933 Classes, 113670 (Box 57, Folder 1)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:53
    - Correspondence Course: Introduction to Scientific Socialism, 1932; 113669 (Box 57, Folder 1)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:54
    - Among the Courses and Lectures, Nov 14, 1932-Dec 23, 1932; 113668 (Box 57, Folder 1)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:55
    - Courses and Lectures, Jan 9, 1933-Apr 7, 1933; 113667 (Box 57, Folder 1)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:56
    - Evening Classes and Lectures, 1933-1934; 113666 (Box 57, Folder 1)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:57